(Penny:)Does NASA know you're using
that thing as a napkin holder?
(Howard:)You kidding? They still think
it's in a secure locker at JPL.
(Penny:)You stole it?
(Howard:)Borrowed.
(Howard:)The trick is to carry it out
to your car like you own it.
(Sheldon(phone gives text alert):)Excuse me.
(Raj:)Oh.
(Sheldon(phone gives text alert):)Amy's at the dry cleaners,
(Sheldon(phone gives text alert):)and she's made a very
amusing pun.
"I don't care
for perchloroethylene,
and I don't like glycol ether."
(Sheldon(phone gives text alert):)Get it?
She doesn't like glycol ether.
Sounds like "either."
"L-O-L."
(Penny:)Who's Amy?
His girlfriend.
(Penny:)Sheldon has a girlfriend?
She's not my girlfriend.